wphackz.com 2017-02-02

# Privacy Policy | WordPress Designs & Themes

This policy explains how we use personal information collected at this site.

 **This is the privacy policy of wphackz.com**

Please read this privacy policy before using the site. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy of wphackz.com

This policy may be changed at any time. Any changes will be posted. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy each and every time you visit wphackz.com

This web site may use cookies to help us collect information about users. We collect certain information about users who visit this site, including user actions and click paths, domain names, IP addresses and browser types, as well as other information. We use this information mainly to track referrals and analyse user behaviour.

 **Sharing Information**  
We may share information with government agencies or other companies helping us to investigate or prevent fraud.

 **We may do so when:**  
(1) Permitted or required to do so by law; or,  
(2) Preventing or attempting to prevent actual or potential unauthorised actions or fraud; or,  
(3) Investigating past fraud. We will not however share user information with third parties for marketing purposes.

This policy of wphackz.com does not cover web sites hyperlinked to or from www.wphackz.com

We are not responsible for the policies of web sites that we hyper link to wphackz.com

If you visit other web sites hyper linked to or from this site, please review the privacy policies at those websites. If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy, please contact wphackz.com
